<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Puffer</string>
    <string name="monitored">Current Connections: </string>
    <string name="life_monitored">Total Checked Connections: </string>
    <string name="blocked_trackers">Blocked Trackers: </string>
    <string name="life_blocked_trackers">Blocked Trackers (Overall): </string>
    <string name="user_protected">Protected</string>
    <string name="user_unprotected">Unprotected</string>
    <string name="switch_off">Switch Off</string>
    <string name="block_lists">Custom Blocklist</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause (30 minutes)</string>
    <string name="resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="please_clear_cache">If adverts are still visible on the testing page please clear your browser cache and try again before filing a report.</string>
    <string name="block_upnp">Block UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) traffic</string>
    <string name="what_is_upnp">UPnP allows devices on your local network to discover each other and communicate. UPnP has been used as a vector for fingerprinting tools, which can use the devices on your local network (LAN) to fingerprint you. Additionally, UPnP has been used as a vector to spread self-propogating through a local network. Blocking UPnP traffic will cause some smart devices like WiFi speakers to stop working. We recommend you disable UPnP traffic if you do not use any smart UPnP LAN devices.</string>
    <string name="block_lan">Block LAN (Local-Area Network) traffic</string>
    <string name="why_block_lan">A LAN (Local-Area Network) is a private network shared between all devices connected to the same router. All devices on a LAN can usually communicate directly, without filtering by the router or firewall. Malware often propagates more easily between locally connected devices due to the relaxed security rules. We recommend that you disable LAN traffic if you frequently use coffee shop WiFi, or other untrusted WiFi hotspots. Disabling LAN will make you unable to communicate directly with local devices, and will stop home NAS or media servers like Plex from working correctly.</string>
</resources>